cgchannel.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy | CG Channel

CG Channel recognizes that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by CG Channel.

**Information we collect and how we use it**  
We offer a number of services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us, such as reading articles or news on CG Channel. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

  * **Information you provide** – When you sign up for a CG Channel account or other CG Channel service or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password).  Primarily, this information is used to enhance the CG Channel community by having less anonymity between members, and thus less harassment and offensive behavior on forums.Under no circumstances does CG Channel sell or provide your contact information to other companies.
  * **Cookies** – When you visit CG Channel, we send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including storing encrypted login information so that you can use CG Channel without having to login every time.
  * **Log information** – When you access CG Channel, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
  * **User communications** – When you send email or other communications to CG Channel, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.
  * **Other sites** – This Privacy Policy applies to CG Channel services only. We do not exercise control over the sites linked to from CG Channel. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.
